I turned Claude Code into a superhuman
creative strategist, and now it works
for me 24/7 analyzing my ad account,
finding me new ad inspiration, and even
creating me ads all without me lifting a
finger. On top of that, I built a
living, self-improving brain that gets
smarter every time me or my team uses
it. And today, I'm going to teach you
exactly how to do that, even if you've
never used Claude Code before. I truly
do believe that the generative coding
tools like Claude Code and Codex are the
biggest opportunity for creative
strategists today to multiply themselves
and make themselves incredibly more
productive with AI. So, today I'm going
to walk you through what they actually
are, how to install the right tools to
make sure everything's set up the
correct way, and then some use cases of
exactly how I use Claude Code to make
myself the 10X marketer and make more
and better ads. So, let's start by
talking about what Claude Code actually
is. See, when you use the regular chat,
you are just beholden to the memory of
Claude Chat or ChatGPT chat uh
remembering everything that you say. The
cool thing about using Claude Code or
Codex is that the memory or context is
actually baked into your local machine
like this, which means it's much better
at retaining information, and then you
can compound this knowledge uh a lot
easier than you can in the chat, which
means it does by nature get smarter uh
every time that you use it. So, instead
of having a chat in Claude AI, you're
actually chatting inside of a folder
that has all of the context about that
specific project. And you can do all the
same things in here that you can do in
the normal Claude Chat. You can have
MCPs in here that generate visuals or do
reports or make artifacts. All things
you can do inside of Claude Chat, you
can do inside of Claude Code. And
because of the fact that it compounds
over time as the more you use it, once
you start using this stuff, there
actually is no reason to ever go back to
the normal Claude Chat because Claude
Code beats it in in every way possible.
Sometimes I use Code Work, but like the
vast majority of my chats now uh are
inside of Claude Code. It can be a bit
intimidating uh when you first get
started, but honestly, once you
understand the file structure um
and you start having conversations here,
you will pick it up. It becomes second
nature, and I I assume that you'll have
the same
uh kind of epiphany and and not ever go
back to the regular Claude chat. It's
like Claude really is like Claude on
steroids.
It is is Claude code. Anyway, let's talk
about the tools that you need to make
this all possible. So, what we're going
to do is going to go to
customize and then connectors. And what
I want you to do is spend some time
thinking about all of the tools that you
use in your ad creative workflow
currently or just in your
in your whole tech stack and add as many
of them to Claude as connectors as
possible. The reason for this is because
Claude code is incredibly powerful on
its own. When you pull in all of these
other tools and have it work inside of
Slack, inside of Notion, inside of
your email, that is when it gets really
really powerful. So, you want to go and
connect all of these as soon as
possible. I have
um
Google Calendar so I can see all my
meeting notes, Gmail obviously. The
Hixfeld MCP is really useful because um
that means we can yeah, make statics and
videos with it. Notion because we do all
of our briefing inside of Notion. Slack
because I want it to ingest all of the
context from Slack. Um and that is most
of them that we'll want to have. Gamma
because we do a lot of our reporting
through this. So, that's also useful as
well. And what you will need for today's
video is the Parker MCP. That's how
we're going to pull in all of the
information from the ad account and
other ad libraries, AI tags, etc. That's
going to make this a lot lot easier to
do. You will need a Parker account for
that. If you want to give this a try for
free, I'm going to leave a a link in the
description below to get a free month of
Parker and try this. All you're going to
want to do is grab this link here that
I'll put in the description. Again, go
to customize
and connectors.
Go to add a custom connector.
And then just call it Parker.
And then you're going to in the
URL and click add and you'll have the
blog MCP inside of here. It's going to
pull all of your ad account data into
here. It's going to pull uh data about
competitors, pull in all your ad tags,
etc. It's a lot that comes with that
that's going to make this process a lot
more powerful. The next thing we're
going to want to do is pull in the
Parker brain. Now, this is the part that
makes it self-improving. Pulls in all
the information from your Slack, from
your Notion, or wherever you do work,
and actually updates the context in your
sleep. What we're going to want to do is
go to this link, which I will link in
the description. Copy the link. Bring it
back inside of our Claude code here, and
we're just going to say I in a folder
that you can create, you know, I've just
got a general Claude code folder
created. You can just say, you know,
I want you to clone this brain
for my brand
X.
Follow the instructions exactly as is.
And you're just going to paste in the
link. And then you're just going to hit
enter. You can do this on Fable 5. It's
going to uh cost you a few hundred bucks
if you do that. Because what's basically
going to happen now is it is going to
run a ton of reports and audits and
generate a lot of context on your brand
that saves to your folder that you're
going to work inside of. And the initial
creation of this is a lot of work, and
it will take a few hours to go and do
this. Uh so I would recommend putting on
auto mode uh so you don't have to keep
accepting um
your permissions and edits. Um but yeah,
just know it will take a bit of time uh
whether you use Fable or Opus. Um
if you want to save money, then I would
do it on Opus. If you want to uh you
just make the absolute best brain
possible, then I would do it on Fable.
But just know it will take a few hours
to generate, and the Fable one will cost
you a few hundred bucks. I would also
strongly recommend having a Max plan
just to generate this. If you have a Max
5X plan on Claude, you will likely run
into 5-hour token limits once or twice.
If you have the 20X plan, you're good to
go. Uh and you should be able to
generate these with uh no issues. But
that is going to be by far the most
token heavy thing that we do here. I
mean, the reason that it it takes so
many tokens is because it's learning and
going so deep on your brand to generate
context that is going to make the
outputs way smarter, which is why this
stuff is important. But, as soon as you
generate the initial,
you know, batch of context, then, you
know, you can downgrade
because you won't you need to be on a
20X plan. So, what's going to happen
after you've done that is just going to
ask you a few simple questions in a
pop-up here. If I go to an actual brand
setup that I did yesterday, uh you know,
it's just going to ask, you know, what's
your main objective, North Star metrics,
just just to learn about your
uh you know, your setup. And then, uh
it's going to go and generate this. And
like I said, it'll take a few hours, but
once it's done, you are ready to get
started in making some of these really
incredible workflows. So, the only thing
you're going to want to do is just open
up a new chat and then go to uh
load up the brain. So, the one that I
just generated there was my Oberpop
client brain. Just going to open that,
trust the workspace, and now we're
working inside of this Oberpop brain.
I'm just going to do the command
get started. And that's going to walk me
through again a little onboarding here
that's going to make sure that all of my
routines are set up. We'll get on to
what they are in a moment. Uh and
everything is in the right place. And
you train the brain on exactly what it
needs to know. And then we can start
getting into the fun stuff. So, let's
actually see in action. What could we do
here? So, I could say, for example, uh I
want you to look through my client
channel
at create Oberpop and uh ingest all of
the feedback the client has ever given
and include this uh in your context
going forward.
Now, because we have set up Slack as a
connector, it's going to look through
the entire channel's history, and any
feedback the client has ever given is
going to bake it into the context here
and going forward anytime that the
client gives feedback inside of Slack,
we know that that is going to flow
through to our client brain and every
time I query inside of Claude code, it
will already have that context. I'm just
going to click always allow and allow it
to run this again. I would recommend
putting on auto mode um
so you don't have to keep accepting
permissions. And this is why it's
important to connect as many tools as
you use with the MCPs into Claude
because then it can ingest all of this
context and it can start outputting. You
can get to start sending messages inside
of Slack. You can get it to uh start
adding things to Notion. For example, I
was in a Claude chat the other day where
I was asking it to come up with ad ideas
every week and then input them into my
idea library inside of Notion. This is
literally the exact idea library that we
use and uh Claude via the Parker MCP was
coming up with ad ideas and adding them
into here completely automatically uh
and then adding links to, you know,
TikToks it was finding or comments that
it was um
referencing from my ads. And this all
comes because I've got my uh Parker set
up in the back end to know all of these
things. So, I have uh the customer
reviews uploaded here. I have
post-purchase surveys, my ad comments uh
flowing automatically inside of here. It
scrolls TikTok for me and finds TikTok
inspiration. Ad library, I've got
competitors that I follow so it knows
what my competitors are. So, all of the
context that you want it to know, I just
basically look at the the web app here
as a as a control room and again, if you
want to try this, there's a there's a uh
link to a free month in the uh in the
description down below. Um and then all
of this information flows through the
MCP into Claude so I can get it to do
these workflows where it says, you know,
look at my competitors and everything
they've launched in the last 30 days and
you know, look at what ad formats
they've run, find their top ads by
impressions and then go and remake them
for us using the Higgsfield MCP. Like
those are the flows that become possible
when you have this Parker MCP that's
pulling in all of the data about your ad
account, your
um
your competitors, uh and then connecting
that to the Parker brain that has all of
this context that self-improves uh over
time. And then actually connects it to
the tools that you use on a day-to-day
basis. So, it comes to you rather than
just, you know, you chatting inside of
Claude all the time. Now, going back to
this chat where it's ingesting uh the
Slack context, you can see it says, "I
read the full ad creative overpop
history from beginning of June 2023 to
today."
Uh and it is now writing into its
context. So, it's gone into Slack,
ingested all of the messages from the
last 3 years, and now it is writing that
into the folder so that all future
queries that you do already has context
of not only the brain, the ad account,
everything inside of Parker, but also
every message ever in Slack. You can do
this for Notion as well. Every concept
you ever produce, you can do this for,
you know, Google Calendar, for every
meeting that you have with the client,
for every internal brainstorm you've
ever done. Like, all of this context
should be going into your client brain
so that it gets smarter every day. And
this is where it becomes really
interesting because, you know, this is
already accounted for if you have the
Parker MCP. We do this automatically for
you. We set up these routines for you.
But you can start setting up routines
that do this on a schedule. Uh so, I go
into my routines here, I can see, you
know, every day uh we've got overpop,
you know, update in the brain, or like
refreshing the context, or generating
new ideas for me. So, all of this stuff
is automatically being updated. Uh so,
it's getting smarter and smarter over
time. Then, when you create any
workflows inside of here, for example,
I was creating a workflow here where I
said, "Look at my external brands' top
static ads by impressions." Again, that
is from uh
Parker. So, look at my external brands,
look at their top ads by impressions. Uh
top static ads by impressions, and uh
find ones that it makes sense for us to
recreate, draft the copy to recreate
them. We would then do through the
Higgsfield MCP. It went and generated
these uh statistics, and you know, I
think the Higgsfield MCP is playing up
here. It sometimes seems to be a little
bit inconsistent with like showing on on
old chats. Uh but just to give you an
idea,
I had it deliver them to me in Slack,
and uh I was pretty
impressed by how well these came out. I
mean, these a lot of these I would say
I'd
genuinely good to go inside the ad
account. I mean, we could do a little
bit of work on the copy,
uh uh
because I literally didn't do any work
on the copy for this. I was just I was
just testing this the other day.
Um but you can get
ads delivered into your Slack, or
wherever you operate, on a Monday
morning, uh just by setting up a
workflow like this, and then saying,
"Okay, now turn this into a uh routine
that runs every morning and pings me
inside of my internal Slack channel."
And again, these, because it's connected
to the Parker MCP, are real
comments or reviews that uh
our customers have have said.
Um so it's not like fabricating this.
It's not getting them from It's not just
making them up itself. I ask go and find
uh real customer reviews or real ad
comments or real post-purchase surveys,
and then infuse them into ads that have
performed for external brands,
and
um
and remake them for us. Then deliver
that to me every Monday morning. You
could have it make 25 ads for you and
send it straight into your Slack every
Monday morning using the Higgsfield MCP,
which again is another one that you want
to set set up here inside of your
Claude. And that's when this just
becomes so incredibly powerful when you
think about all the different tools you
have, and then just start connecting
them together, and having it proactively
deliver them to you uh on a schedule
inside of the place that you already
work. You know, uh I mean, spoke about a
gamma earlier. Uh another report that I
uh another thing that I did was I said,
"Build my monthly creative port report."
Again, this is like a super simple
prompt. You can probably make something
way, way better than this.
Um I just want a performance story of
the time. Tell me what's working, what's
not working, and uh and then ground it
in customer evidence. And I made it make
that inside of Gamma.
And here's what it did. So, it's
literally put together this whole report
with everything that I need. Uh you
know, we at Create do retros every
month. We have to produce a report just
like this
uh and then send it to the team
internally, then send it to the client.
This has been done in one prompt with no
optimization. I could say, you know, go
and
uh you know, index more on competitors,
or go and do more organic research.
Because you are tapped into everything
through the Parker MCP, you can get to
report on performance. You can get to
report on competitors. You can get it to
look at, you know, our customer voice
and compare it against uh the ad account
and see what opportunities we're
missing. You can get it to look at the
organic feed. You can get it to look at
ad comments. For example, it says here,
uh the most liked comment in the last 60
days is uh he's like my 16 and a half
year old newborn. It's talking about
dogs here cuz this is a dog brand.
That's a really
uh really nice piece of copy uh and an
angle that we actually haven't tested
yet, which is flagged inside of the ad
account. And it got 46 likes as well as
a comment um most liked comment in the
last 60 days. So, that is a a good
signal that we might want to start
making ads around senior dogs. And all
of this stuff is just put together in
this one report that we've made through
one prompt, um which is pretty insane.
Again, here it's gone on the organic
feed and found content that we might
want to recreate. It's looked at our
other brands inside of Parker and and
looked at what they're testing right now
and and and given us suggestions. There
are so many things that you could go and
uh build off the back of this. The world
really is your oyster when you get into
cloud code and you get into producing
things like this. Here's another report
that I made in Google Slides. Another
one that looked at competitive vars and
uh compared us to the gap analysis and
then used that to come up with ad ideas
based on our voice of customer. Imagine
having a V1 of your monthly report that
you send to, you know, your performance
team, your strategy team, your client,
whatever it is, delivered to you inside
of Slack every single month saying,
"Here's the V1 of the report. Approve it
and I'll send it off to the relevant
stakeholders or go and edit inside of
Gamma or give me feedback and I'll know
for next time." And that's the cool
thing here is that you can literally, if
I didn't like this for whatever reason,
I could go into Claude code and I can
say, "When you're doing reporting, you
seem to over-index on, you know, ROAS or
CPA. I care more about the ads that get
the most spend inside the ad account.
From now on, I want you to remember it
this and in all future reports that you
do, always prioritize that metric." And
then the brain will take that feedback
on board, write it into its system, and
then know for next time that that's how
you do reporting. If we go back to the
original query that we had about uh
getting the Slack that's updated, you'll
see that it's now completed that. It has
wrote it into the folder. If I go into
the folder, this is the output folder
that we made. Uh I can see that if I go
into running notes as it said here, we
can see it's got a client feedback
document. It has created this document.
I did not create this document. It has
taken in my query and created the client
feedback document. It's going to update
that as more context comes in from
Slack, comes in from Google Calendar,
comes in from email, or wherever you
want to connect, and this system gets
smarter. Uh this folder gets smarter and
therefore your Claude gets smarter uh
the more that you use it. I do just want
to highlight the effectiveness of the
static ads workflow again. This has been
one of my favorite use cases of the
Parker MCP and the Parker brain so far
and Claude code in general. Uh because
here I said, you know, "Search my
customer reviews and Facebook ad
comments. Find the most emotionally
loaded phrases that our that our
customers are telling us.
Uh cluster them into distinct angles.
Look at the Facebook ads data, and then
basically use these to create some
statics for us, and then using the
Hixfeld MCP, it generated these, which
again, I have not, you know, done a pass
on the copy here, but this is, you know,
this is the phrase that we saw from the
report, so it knows, you know, where our
white space is, where we haven't tested
inside the ad account yet, what personas
we have not here, and I can tell you,
because we do the ads for this account,
we have not really hit the senior dog
angle that hard yet.
Kind of That is a That is a ready to go
static that I would launch inside that
account. That's very good. And this is a
real customer comment or review that
they have said, so we can use that and
put it into the account. Um
So, just just setting up this workflow
and getting these delivered into your
Slack every Monday is just such a lock,
and you can put out so many more
statics. You can do it for video as
well, but you need a little bit more
human in the loop for that, I found. Um
but statics it just such like statics
and reporting it it's so so good for
this, and getting it to populate your
ideas bank, like we showed it in in
Notion, whether you have your awesome or
else, you can do that, too. The amount
of The amount of workflows you can just
set up off the back of this are, you
know, absolutely insane. And again,
anything you want to turn into a
schedule, you can just say, "Turn this
into a routine."
I can't spell, and send this to me on
Slack
every Monday. Or you can just go and set
up the routine in the routine section,
and you can have it here. But, you know,
if you use the Parker Brain, then we're
going to set up a a bunch of these
routines for you, so it will
self-update, it will dream, it will
refresh the context, it will come up
with ad ideas for you every single week.
Uh create research loops. Loops and
judges is a whole another video I can
get into as well. There is so so much
that you can get into here. And as a
reminder, the outputs will be as good as
you have your Parker set up on the back
end, so make sure you're following
brands inside of here that tagged as,
you know, affinity brands, which are,
you know, brands that are, you know,
selling to the same audience, but not
the same product, competitors, inspo
brands. Make sure you have those set up.
You've got AI tagging on every single
one of the ads, even your competitors'
ads, so you can ask, you know, look at
Caraway's ads and give me a breakdown by
ad format. Every ad in our database is
ranked by impressions, so you can kind
of see what's performing for other
brands. Uh you can say, you know, look
at the Caraway's top ads by impressions
and try and find some common themes in,
you know, the emotions or desires or ad
formats or just in general. Um you got
the same thing in the performance tab.
You can say look at my swipe file, look
at my ideas. Uh basically anything that
you can query inside of Parker, uh you
can query inside of the Claude MCP. Now,
Reddit you do not have access to yet. We
are working on that. It's close, so I'm
very excited to to release that to you
guys, but everything else inside of the
app um you can you can query inside of
the MCP um and get it to turn into ads
for your brand.
So, if you want to give this whole
workflow a try, I'm going to give you a
link to get a free month of Parker to
try completely free. All you would need
to do is generate the brain inside of
your Claude code. So, click the link in
the description below. You can get a
free month of Parker. Try this
completely risk-free and uh
really just step into this new world.
I'm so excited for you guys because
genuinely, once you start using Claude
code or Codex, there is no reason to go
back to regular chat. There is no reason
to ever have a chat in Claude AI again
once you've got these brains set up for
uh your brand and I'm so excited for to
see the use cases that you come out with
cuz I'm sure there's a bunch of other
things that I've even, you know, thought
of that you guys can do with this with
all the different tools you're going to
connect. Anyway, if you like this video,
hit subscribe, comment what you want to
see more of, and um I will see you in
the next one.